自天地初開之時
[Man Narrating] Since time began...
世界就被一場在
a war has been waged in the shadows...
正義和邪惡之間的戰爭所籠罩著
between the armies ofGood and Evil.
這場戰爭可能驚天地泣鬼魂
It may be fought on a grand scale...
也可能只是在小孩之間的心魔之戰
or within the heart ofa single individual-or even a child.
邪惡力量無處不在
The Evil has taken many forms...
它被黑暗所支配著
and used the darkest ofarts.
在現代，他們被稱作
In our time, they call themselves simply...
幻影殺手
the Hand.
正義總是站在善良的一方
The Good follow the way ofki magure.
仁慈之主不但可以看到未來
Its masters can see the future...
甚至能夠起死回生
and perhaps even bring back the dead.
這是個武魂的傳奇故事
Legend tells of a unique warrior...
她是一顆失落的靈魂
a lost soul.
她是個女戰士
This warrior is a woman...
她是個孤兒
a motherless daughter.
上天安排她去平息這場 正義與邪惡之戰
And it is her destiny to tip the balance between Good and Evil.
有個小孩是力量之源 雙方都需要她的協助
She is a treasure, and both sides seek her out...
她將成為戰爭中的終極武器
as a final weapon in an ancient war.
片名：艾麗卡 又名：幻影殺手
- 你那有什麼動靜嗎？ - 一切正常
- [ Man ] Perimeter, what's your status? - [ Man #2 ] Delta team, clear.
- 一切正常 - 一切正常
- [ Man #3 ] Alpha, clear. - [ Man #4 ] Bravo, secure.
沒有用的
It doesn't matter.
你阻止不了她的
You can't stop her.
- 沒人能阻止她 - 就憑她？
- Nobody can stop her. - Her?
恐怕這次你無法完成任務
I was afraid if I told you, you wouldn't take the job.
我本來是不想請你出山的
I never should've hired you.
衝你來的那個人到底是誰？
Who doyou think's coming foryou?
你也許聽說過她，她叫…
You may have heard ofher. Her name...
艾麗卡
is Elektra.
- 你覺得這個很好笑嗎？ - 她是城裡一段傳奇
- You find that funny? - She's an urban legend, sir.
幾年前就死了
That woman died years ago.
真的？ 那應該派人把她的屍體帶回來
Really? Well, then somebody must have brought her back from the dead.
鮑爾，知道嗎？ 我們的所作所為
You know, Bauer, whenyou've done the things I've done...
給我們樹立了好多敵人
you make a lot of enemies.
我花巨款買來的密報說
My private security detail- the best money could buy.
這個死掉的女人 在半個小時內殺了14個人
This nonexistent woman killed 1 4 of them in half an hour.
我都不敢離開這裡
I barelygot away.
奇怪的是，在蒙特卡洛時 她居然放過我
Spent the next two days in Monte Carlo wondering why she let me go.
而現在卻又向我殺來
Then she came for me.
原本是幻影殺手負責我的安全 而她曾經是他們的一分子
I was underthe protection ofthe Hand itself, who sent theirbest.
現在組織為了殺她 已經不管我得死活
Although theyseemed more interested in killing Elektra than in protecting me.
把這些保鏢碾個粉碎
She cut 'em down I i ke wheat.
她只需要10分鐘，最多15分鐘
T ook maybe 1 0, 1 5 m i nutes max.
我不能再袖手旁觀
Didn't really think why I kept gettin' away.
這是我來的目的
So here I am.
我現在瞭解她了
And now I understand her.
她想讓我嘗嘗這種滋味
She wanted me to feel this...
像是走頭無路
what it's like to have nowhere to go...
無人求援
nowhere to turn.
你現在感覺怎麼樣？
How's yourperimeter doing now?
德爾塔，你那裡情況怎麼樣？
Delta, what's your status?
沒有反應 臭婊子
There's no signal. Son of a bitch.
- 你知道嗎，這種刺客喜歡 - 阿爾法，布萊歐，請回答
- You know, the better the assassin- -Alpha, Bravo, report!
在你知道她的行蹤之前 她會先慢慢逼近，然後幹掉你
the closer they can get to you before you know they're there.
阿爾法，布萊歐，請回答
Alpha! Bravo! Report!
該死
- [ Static ] - Ah, Christ.
他們說在艾麗卡殺你之前 會在你耳邊說悄悄話
They say Elektra whispers in your ear before she kills you.
- 阿爾法，布萊歐，請回答 - 老闆現在太晚了，鮑爾
- Alpha! Bravo! Report! - [ Woman ] It's too late foryour boss, Bauer.
- 但你還是有機會的 - 哦，該死
- But you still have a chance. -Jesus Christ!
你無法與鬼魂戰鬥
[Woman ] You can't fight a ghost, Bauer.
該到我們了
- Here we are at last. - [ Exhales ]
跟傳說的一模一樣
Guess it's all true.
紅色的衣服 還有那把刀
The red outfit and the knives and-
現在你想怎麼樣？
So, what happens now?
毫不猶豫地殺了我？
You just kill me, straight out? Just cold?
不要怕 死亡並不是一件很可怕的事
Don't worry. Death's not that bad.
是嗎？你怎麼知道？
Yeah? How do you know?
我已經死過一次
[ Whispering ] I died once.
是什麼感覺？ 有沒有...
What's it like? Is there...
白光和上帝？
you know, a white light and God?
我想 我就要知道了
What- I guess I'll find out.
我也明白幻影殺手的力量
So am I to understand that with all the power ofthe Hand...
我們的頭號殺手 還在躲避著我們？
that the Treasure continues to elude us?
對，我們本應該更早點採取行動
Yes. Perhaps ifwe had pursued it sooner...
向她發動更大的攻勢
and more aggressively-
你膽敢怪罪幫主羅侍郎？
You dare to blame Master Roshi?
也許克阮你太掉以輕心了
Seems our methods are too mild for Kirigi.
根本沒有
Not at all, sensei.
如果我們不能得到這個力量之源
But ifwe cannot have the weapon ourselves...
也不能讓她落入敵人的手裡
allow me to make sure it does not fall into the hands ofthose who may use it against us.
幫主，請讓我插幾句
Master, allow me.
這個事情一定要盡快地 悄悄地解決
Things like this must be handled smoothly, quietly.
那就悄悄地去辦吧，馬之密 但一定要快
Then work smoothly, Meizumi, but quickly.
克阮
Kirigi?
什麼事？爸爸
Yes, Father.
耐心點
Patience.
你怎麼門都不鎖 一點安全意識都沒有
[Man ] You think that's safe, leaving the door unlocked like that?
艾麗卡，一顆子彈就能結束你
Geez, Elektra, you're gonna end up with a bullet in your head.
我給你帶了點東西
I brought you a little something.
等下，不要放在那裡 我剛剛擦好
No, stop, McCabe. Don't put it down. I al ready cleaned there.
- 為什麼你整天的清洗這裡？ - 擦除我的DNA
- Why do you always do this? - Get rid of my D.N.A.
啊，DNA，說得沒錯
Ah, D.N.A., of course. Right.
我真傻，這個是我剛拿到的 你一定想看看
Silly of me. Listen, I just picked this up. I knowyou like to look.
- 全部在裡面了？ - 連我的一成也沒到
- It's all there? - Less my 1 0%.
- 到巴巴多斯島拿一半 - 還有一半要到馬恩島拿
- Halfto Barbados? - And halfto the bank on the Isle of Man.
其實你可以賺更多 我知道一個人，我幫你聯繫他
You can do better in mutual funds. I know a guy. I could putyou in touch-
- 不用了，謝謝 - 不要了？但是...
- No, thanks. - Or not. But-
聽我說，其實我不想干涉你的事情
Look, I don't want to tell you how to doyour thing...
但是這一次 有很多人搶這個生意
but quite a body count on this one, E.
難道我們只能為丹馬克賣命
We were only getting paid for DeMarco.
非得這樣嗎？
Was it necessary?
是不得不
Had to be done.
是嗎？
Did it?
艾麗卡
Elektra.
是嗎？
Did it?
好吧
Okay.
我們要緊尊師父的教誨
Anyway, it spreads the legend.
否則，我會死的
Besides, theywere gonna kill me.
這個說的沒錯
Of course they were. Absolutely.
但是聽你的特工小組說
And, speaking ofwhich, as your agent...
這是一件及其重要的任務
I am obligated to tell you we just got an absolutely fantastic new offer...
- 也是你最後的任務 - 我們不要談這個了，我需要休息一下
- but that last job- - Let's skip this one. I need a breather.
- 那好吧，我只是說這次報酬很高 - 我已經很累了
- Great idea. I'm just sayin' it's a lot of coin. - I'm tired.
你真的累了？ 那你還真需要好好睡一覺
You're tired? Well, then you better getyourselfsome sleep...
否則你很快會垮掉的
'causeyou are gonna crash, baby, you know that.
你好像從來都沒有休息過的樣子
I mean, you even get laid?
這次任務報酬真的很多
It's a lot of money, this new offer.
- 曼柯 - 好，好吧
- McCabe. - All right, fine. You know what?
那你慢慢休息一下 你想行動的時候打電話給我
Look, you want to take time off, take time off. Call me when you wanna work.
多少錢？說吧
How much? And just tell me.
兩百萬
Two.
他們也可能雇其他殺手
Ah, they'll give it to somebody else.
他們不會付給別人這麼多的
Theywouldn't pay that to somebody else.
你說得對
You got that right.
他們很想你去處理這件事
They asked specifically foryou.
地點在那裡面 找到目標以後通知你
Location's in there. I'll call you when I get the target.
好好睡會吧
Get some sleep.
再試一次
- Again! - [ Man ] Clear!
你知道你的方向嗎，艾麗卡
[Man's Voice ] Doyou knowthe way, Elektra?
意念，可以讓你控制時間
[Man's Voice Continuing] Kimagure, the abilityto control time...
看到未來
the future...
甚至可以起死回生
even life and death.
我知道我是這裡最好的學生
[ Elektra ] I know I'm the best student here.
不是最好的 但是最有力量的
Not the best. The most powerful.
你明白暴力和痛苦
You understand violence and pain.
但你還沒有領悟到突破的出路
But you do not know the way.
- 那請你教我吧 - 這個我辦不到
- Teach me then. - That's my point.
這個不是教出來的
I can't teach you.
我要你離開這裡
I want you to go.
這個算是測驗嗎？師傅
Is this a test, sensei?
不是測驗
No, not a test.
走吧
Just go.
我沒有地方去
I don't have anywhere to go.
委託人說要你 早幾天到行動地點
[McCabe ] The clientsays he needsyou there a couple days early...
這也是你的報酬中的部分行動
says that's part ofthe deal.
- 為什麼 - 不知道
- [ Elektra ] Why? - No idea.
- 他只是想你在那裡等他消息 - 看來我不得不去了
- He just wants you to wait. - I just want to get this over with.
我知道，其實那裡的風景不錯
Hey, me too. Listen, why don't you tell me about the view?
聽說那裡風景秀麗 你知道，如果你到...
I hear it's gorgeous out there. You know, you got the-
繼續艾麗卡，堅持住
- [Man ] Come on, Elektra. Keep pedaling. - [ Gasps ]
再堅持5分鐘
Five more minutes.
不要用手 別想偷懶，只能用腳
Don't use your hands. Don't be lazy. Only use your feet.
堅持住 踩水，踩水...
Let's go! Let's push, push, push, push!
尼姑拉斯，親愛的，該休息了 她只是個孩子
Nikolas. Honey, please. She'sjust a kid.
繼續，艾麗卡
[Nikolas ] Keep going, Elektra.
繼續踩
Keep going.
天哪，你瘋了 你差點殺了我
Jesus! What's the matter with you? You could have killed me!
你在這裡幹嗎？
What are you doing here?
沒什麼 我只是在這裡隨便走走
Nothing. I'm friends with the Wheelwrights.
真實糟糕 你把我的大衣弄壞了
[ Sighs ] Damn it. You cut my friggin' jacket.
- 你怎麼進去的？ - 門根本就沒有鎖
- How did you get in? - The front doorwas unlocked.
- 不可能 - 它是沒有鎖
- No, it wasn't. - Yeah, it was.
住在這裡的人都讓我隨便出入 不信你去問
[ Sighs ] Look, the people who live here let me come in all the time. Ask anybody.
好像是壞了
Hmm. It's broken.
- 你是？我的名字是艾比 - 你偷了什麼東西
- So, who areyou anyways? My name's Abby. - What'd you steal?
什麼都沒有 你把我當成什麼？
[ Sighs ] Nothing. What doyou think I am?
求你不要叫警察
Please don't call the cops.
我老爸會打死我的
My dad will kill me.
在某些地方的只是要 剁掉小偷的手
In some parts ofthe world, theyjust cutyour hands off.
你怎麼弄得？
How did you do that?
給我離開這裡
Get out ofhere.
不要擔心，艾麗卡
[Man, Distorted] Don't worry, Elektra.
我會好好照顧她的
I'll take good care ofher.
媽媽?
Mom?
哦，媽的
Oh, shit.
我坐不住了，曼柯 快點告訴我目標
[Elektra ] You know I can't sit still, McCabe. Call me with the name.
委託人想讓你早點到那裡 在那兒等幾天
[ McCabe ] Client says he needs you there a couple days early. Wants you to wait.
-　哪兒也不要去 - 死亡並不是那麼可怕
- [ DeMarco's Voice ] To have nowhere to go- - Death 's not that bad.
- 無人求援 - 他只是想讓你等著
- nowhere to turn. - He wants you to wait.
- 難道就這樣殺了我？ - 他想你在那裡等著
- Youjust kill me, straight out? - He wants you to wait.
你在找我嗎？
[ Elektra ] Are you looking for me?
你好
H i.
你是新來的房客嗎？
Are you the new, uh, tenant?
房產經紀人埃迪說 這個月有位年輕的小姐搬來
Eddie Ferris, the Realtor- he said, uh, a young woman had taken it for the month.
關你什麼事？
What do you want?
對不起，我也許不該說這個
Sorry. This is kind of awkward, but, uh...
你有沒有看到一個13歲 金髮的女孩
haveyou seen a girl- 1 3-year-old, uh, blondish hair to about here?
她是我女兒，艾比
My daughter, Abby.
- 我們昨天吵了一架 - 我下午看到她的
- We hada fightyesterday- - I saw her late afternoon.
- 哦，是嗎？ - 我闖到了我家裡
- Oh, you did? - She broke into my house.
真是氣人
Shit. Really?
她總是到處亂跑
Uh, she knows the Wheelwrights, who, uh-
那她拿你什麼東西沒？
She, uh, didn't take anything, did she?
- 沒有 - 那就好
- No. - Good.
如果她打壞你什麼東西，我會賠給你 我叫馬克·米勒
Look, if she broke something, I'm- I'm happy to pay for it. I'm Mark Miller.
住在那個木屋裡，隔你兩間房
We're in the little cabin two houses down.
那好吧，謝謝
Okay, thanks.
我是曼柯 只要留下你的名字
[McCabe ] Hi,you've reached McCabe. But please leavejustyour name.
- 請不要留言 - 曼柯
- Do not leave a message. - [ Sighs ] McCabe...
我再坐在這裡，就要發瘋了
I 'm sick of sitting here.
如果你在弄不到對方的名字 我要離開這裡了
We don't get a name soon, I'm walking.
嗨
Hey.
你站在那裡多久了？
How long have you been standing there?
大概一分鐘
Like, a minute.
你都跟我爸說了些什麼？
What did you tell my dad?
你告訴他，我闖到你家去了嗎？
Did you tell him I broke intoyour house?
- 說了，因為你的確去了 - 你幹嗎非告訴他
- Yeah, becauseyou did break in. - Well, you didn't have to tell him.
我還以為你不會計較呢
I thoughtyou were cool.
- 可惜我不是 - 沒錯，一點都不會騙人
- I'm not. - Yeah, no kidding.
我爸讓我來邀請你去 跟我們共進聖誕晚餐
Now he's on my case. He made me come askyou to have Christmas dinnerwith us.
- 什麼？
- Have what? - Christmas?
聖誕晚餐，12月25號
Dinner? December25?
你知道今天是聖誕節嗎？
Did you know today's Christmas?
謝謝你，但是我不能去 我有事情要做
Thankyou. I can't. I have something to do.
什麼事，所有的店都關門了
What? Everything's closed.
你現在在一個孤島上
You're on an island.
求你了，來吧
Come on. Please?
每天晚上都是我們兩個
It's just the two of us every night...
我都厭倦這種生活了
and I'm bored out of my skull.
你在幹嘛？
What areyou doing?
沒幹嗎，為什麼？
Nothing. Why?
- 你在數什麼？ - 沒有啊
- Wereyou counting? - No.
你會來的是吧，求你了
So, will you come? Please?
如果你不來，我還會偷到你家去
Because ifyou don't, I'll just keep breaking intoyour house. Hmm?
那我要去換下衣服
Hmm. I have to change my clothes.
太好了
Great!
我叫艾比
I'm Abby.
艾麗卡
Elektra.
艾麗卡，不錯
Elektra. Cool.
跟你講了不要出去
I told you not to leave the house.
- 你根本就不知道我出去了 - 艾比
- You didn't even know I was gone. - Abby.
先暫停爸爸 我們有個客人
Chill, Dad. We have a guest.
對不起 她說是你要她去邀請我的
I'm sorry. She told me that you'd invited me.
我本不想來
I don't want to-
- 我只是
- I'll just- - Hmm. Uh-uh.
沒關係的，一起吃飯吧
- [Footsteps Departing] - No. Please, stay.
我很高興你能來
I'm- I'm gladyou're here.
你要喝點啤酒還是紅酒？
Uh, can I get you a beer? Wine?
水
Water.
她叫艾麗卡，爸爸
Her name's Elektra, Dad.
艾麗卡
- ** [ Continues ] - Elektra.
奇怪的名字 你父母一定很幽默吧
Like the tragedy. Your parents must have had a sense of humor.
一點都不
Not really.
爸爸，當她看我這個美男子 像是超越了她所有的朋友
[Abby] So when she sees all the cute guys who like me- just as friends, Dad-
她決定把我畫在泰姬陵的牆上 作為他們的代表
she accidentally spills posterpaint all over my model ofthe Taj Mahal.
後來我在她的鼻子上塗了點膠水
So I put gl ue on her shoes.
結果她停止了計劃畫我的工程 後來由於打架我被趕出了那裡
I got suspended for that, and then I got expelled for fighting.
這就是我在...
But that was way back in the day in- in, um...
巴爾的摩的童年生活
Baltimore.
我很好奇你為什麼租了 惠爾萊特的房子
So, I was a little surprised to seeyou take the Wheelwright place.
因為很少有人 會在這個時候租他的房子的
Not manyrenters this time ofyear.
我是為工作，在這裡住一個月
It's just for the month, forwork.
你是幹什麼的？
What do you do anyway?
專門做些解僱人
Oh, layoffs, payroll reduction.
縮減工人薪水之類的事情
- That sort ofthing. - Hmm.
- 聽上去很無聊的樣子 - 艾比
- Sounds boring. - Abby.
沒錯，是很無聊 我很喜歡你的手鐲
No, it is boring. I like your bracelet, by the way.
你知道它代表什麼嗎？
Do you know what those are? Here.
這是源於印尼水晶珠 它代表武士道精神
They're warrior beads. They're from Indonesia.
在古代，只有村莊 最好的武士才配戴它
Centuries ago, you had to be the best fighter in yourvillage to earn them.
我從網上買的
I bought 'em off eBay.
這島上有學校嗎？
Is there a school here on the island?
我們打算先進行一段家庭式的教育
Uh, we're tryinghomeschooling fora while.
我讀過大學的書 自己也可以學代數
I read at college level. And I'm doing algebra one on my own.
她是個不錯的學生
She's a goodstudent.
但是他的行為卻總是讓我失望
It's the, uh, behavioral stuff that's been a problem.
我有權力干自己喜歡的事 我沒有必要非聽那些嘮叨
I have authority issues, and I don't take bullshit well.
- 不要這樣對你爸說 - 嗨，艾比
- Don't speak in that- - Hey, Abby!
沒關係
It's okay.
這麼快她已經是個大人了
Suddenly I got a teenager on my hands.
- 其實她很努力 - 你可以直接跟她說
- She's hard on herself. - You can tell, huh?
- 很多人認為她很懶 - 不，我不認為
- Most people think she's a slacker. - No, I shouldn't.
聖誕快樂
Merry Christmas?
她媽媽呢？
Where's her mother?
她很多年前就死了
She died... a couple ofyears ago.
在巴爾的摩？
Back in Baltimore?
對，酒後駕車
Yeah. Drunk driver.
我很小的時候媽媽就死了
My mother died when I was young.
我應該回去了
I should go.
- 我還有工作要做 - 不是吧，天還早呢
- I have work. - Come on, it's early.
多謝晚餐
Thanks for dinner.
媽媽
Mom.
- 什麼事？
- [ Beeps ] - What?
看你的郵包
[ McCabe ] Good morning. You just got a delivery.
- 這次是兩個人 - 所以賺雙份錢
- It's a double. - Which makes double the money.
這正是賺這麼多錢的原因
Yeah, that's why the big bucks.
- 怎麼了？ - 沒事
- What's the matter? - Nothing.
好吧，沒問題最好
Good. Then there'll be no problems.
解決了我會打電話給你
I'll call you when it's done.
你的數學怎麼樣了？
How's math going?
你覺得呢？
How doyou think it's going?
什麼，你居然沒殺他們 是現在不行還是永遠不行
What doyou mean, you're not doing it? Not now or not ever?
- 有太多因素了，背景比較複雜 - 背景？
- Too manyvariables. Not enough background. - Background?
好吧，那聖誕節到明尼蘇打洲怎樣？
Okay, well, how about, uh, born in Minnesota on Christmas Day.
想不想看冰魚和龍這部電影？
Enjoys, uh, ice fishing and dragon movies.
我要離開這裡 我定下來再給你電話
McCabe, I'm out ofhere. I'll call you when I land someplace.
他們會馬上派別人來的
They'll just send somebody else, E.
我們所預測的暴風雨終於降臨了
The storm we've been waiting- all- finally here.
- 暴風雨移到了西雅圖的塔科馬地區 - 我到倉庫去拿沙袋
- It's moved into the Seattle-Tacoma area. - I'll getsandbags from the shed.
他們在說笑吧，說得這麼激動 這只是一場雨而已
You know, this is such a joke. They make it sound all exciting, but you know it's just rain.
你如果不是很忙 就把窗戶粘好
Ifyou're not too busy, young lady, feel free to tape the windows.
馬上去
Now!
馬克
Mark!
我能跟你談談嗎？
Can I talk to you?
我們能進屋說嗎？
Can we talk inside?
當然可以
Yeah, sure.
嗨，到底什麼事？
Hey, what's up?
艾比，你能先去裡面房間嗎？ 我要跟你爸談事情
Can you go to your bedroom for a minute, Abby? I need to talk to your dad.
快去
Now!
去吧，艾比
Go, Abby.
- 你到底是誰？跟我說實話 - 什麼?
- Who are you? Don't lie to me. - What?
他們不僅要殺你
Theywon'tjust killyou.
還要殺了艾比
They'll kill Abby.
- 媽的 - 爸爸
- Damn it! - Dad!
快走
Go!
快跑艾比 到浴室去，快點跑
Run, Abby! Bathroom! Go! Go! Go!
- 別離開艾比 - 好的
- Staywith Abby! - Okay.
艾比
[Mark ] Abby!
- 艾麗卡 - 艾比
- Elektra! - Abby!
誰派你來的？
[ Speaking Japanese ]
你很快就知道了
壞了
Damn it.
退後
Get back!
快點退後
Get back! Go!
走
[ Mark] Go.
他們馬上就會到
There'll be more coming.
而且更厲害
What's coming next will be worse.
我想克阮對幻影理事會有話要說
I believe Kirigi wishes to address the Council ofthe Hand.
尊敬的主人
Venerable master...
儘管你是如此的精明能幹
despite your delicacy and subtlety...
你卻沒能處理好能量之源
you have failed to solve the problem ofthe Treasure.
羅侍郎幫主已經把這個任務交給我
Master Roshi gave that task to me.
- 沒錯 - 我的手下會處理好的
- Yes, exactly. - And my men are taking care of it.
你的手下已經死了
Your men are dead!
是被那個殺手艾麗卡殺的
Killed bythe female, Elektra, the gaijin.
專橫的人讓人可恨
Your forces are an abomination!
羅侍郎幫主
Master Roshi...
幻影組織絕不能 失去這一代的能量之源
the Hand cannot afford to lose the Treasure for another generation.
所以我誠心的要求接受這個任務
So I humbly request you allow me this task.
也許我還是比較適合的
Perhaps with a little less delicacy...
至少我是不會輸給一個女人
my forces will not be defeated by a mere woman.
這個任務就交給你了
The task is yours.
好好完成它 把你的領導能力證明給理事會
Complete it, andyou will have proven yourselfworthy ofleading this council.
我會置身事外
I will step aside.
幻影殺手的人
[ McCabe ] The Hand ofall people.
這次誰幫你擺平這件事情
So who's gonna help you out on this one, E?
- 斯迪克？ - 告訴我他的地址
- Stick? -J ust give me his location.
沒問題 我有把握
Sure, no problem. I got it handled.
該死的
Goddamn it.
輪到你了，盲人
[ Sighs ] You're up, blind man.
你雙色，我要連進兩球然後反彈再進三球 順序是4 3 2 1 6
Double combo: triple carom on the four-three-two-one-six with a bank masse.
你不用把所有的都想像到這一槍上 這只是第一槍
Uh, you don't need to call all your shots, Pops.Just the first one.
沒錯就要這第一槍
That is the first one.
哇，你真會跟我開玩笑
Whoa, whoa. Aw, you gotta be kidding me.
8號球在角落裡
Eight ball in the corner.
- 盲人？臭屁阿 - 把你的錢放在台桌上
- Blind, myass. - Leave your money on the table.
給你點錢去玩會彈球
Here's a dollar, Abs. Go play some pinball.
- 為什麼總是趕我走 - 快去
- Why do I always have to miss the good stuff? -Just go.
艾麗卡，還是那樣的走路方式
Elektra. Same walk.
那一種香水
Same perfume.
他們需要你的幫助
They need your help.
到這兒來
Over here.
這是馬克·米勒
This is Mark Miller.
馬克和他女兒被幻影殺手追殺
Mark and his daughter, Abby, are being chased by the Hand...
他們需要你的保護
andtheyneedyourprotection.
我把他們留在你這裡 殺手你來應付，然後我就不管了
I'm leaving them with you. The Hand is your business, not mine.
對了，克阮 他們已經派克阮來了
Ah, Kirigi. They've sent Kirigi.
媽的
Shit.
你有沒有問他們 殺手為什麼要追殺他們？
Didyou everask whythe Hand was afterthem?
- 他們不知道 - 真的？米勒你不知道?
- They don't know. - Really? Mr. Miller doesn't know?
其實我知道
I do know.
幻影殺手想要的東西 他卻不想給
The Hand wantedsomething he couldn't give.
他想逃跑
He tried to run.
然後呢？
And what?
他們殺了我妻子，艾比的媽媽
They killed my wife, Abby's mom.
她不是酒後駕車 是我撒謊了
There was no drunk driver. I lied.
你自己的事情自己解決吧
You're on your own.
你到底為什麼要救他們，艾麗卡？
Why didyou reallysave them, Elektra?
難道是為了懺悔？ 為你所作所為贖罪？
Some kind of penance? A down payment on your sins?
她告訴你她實際是幹什麼的了 米勒先生？
Has she toldyou what she actually does for a living, Mr. Miller?
她救了我和我的女兒 這個已經足夠了
She saved my life and my daughter's. That's enough for me.
而你想利用她對你的好感
Thenyou landed on the luckyside ofthe street.
該死你說什麼
- Damn, you son of a bitch! - Because with most people-
艾麗卡
Well, Elektra...
你一點沒變
you haven't changed.
我們去哪？
What are we gonna do?
艾麗卡？ 我們到底去哪？
Elektra? What are we gonna do?
你快點逃命吧 越遠越好，越快越好
You gotta run. As far as you can, as fast as you can.
南美，非洲 改名換姓，改容換貌
SouthAmerica. Africa. Changeyourname. Changeyourappearance.
- 你不跟我們一塊走？ - 不
- You're not coming with us? - No.
- 我不能 - 為什麼不？你難道沒有什麼藏身之處？
- I can't. - Why not? Isn't that part ofyour code or something?
我沒有，艾比
I don't have a code, Abby.
- 那我們怎麼保護自己？ - 我們沒有事的，艾比
- How are we supposed to defend ourselves? - We'll be okay, Abby.
我們根本不行
No, we won't.
醒醒吧爸爸，我們力單物薄
Wake up, Dad. We won't!
他們要殺了我們 像對付媽媽那樣
They're gonna hunt us down. Just like Mom.
快點進車
[ Breathing Heavily ] Get in the car.
Get in the car!
怎麼了？
What's wrong?
她就在下一條街 離停車場三個街區
She's down the street. Three blocks over in the parking lot.
我們要先殺了那個女刺客
We need to kill the gaijin assassin first.
我們現在就動手嗎？
Should we go now?
這兒不行 繼續跟蹤他們
Not here. Keep track ofthem.
我是一個殺手
I'm a soccer mom.
那你真的靠殺人為生？
So, you, um- you really kill people for a living?
對
Yeah.
為什麼？
Why?
因為我只會這個
It's what I'm good at.
這種生活好像很難過
That's messed up.
沒錯
Yeah.
哎，哎 你這魯莽的殺手
Well, well, the reluctant assassin.
很抱歉托你下水，曼柯
Sorry to drag you into this, McCabe.
我也很抱歉
Me too.
你好，我是艾比
Hi. I'mAbby.
你好艾比，不要站在這裡了
Hello, Abby. I'm wondering whatyou're doing here.
我客房很多 趕快到裡面去吧，不用客氣哦
There's plentyofroom in the house. Go aheadand helpyourselves to whateveryou need.
- 謝謝 - 不客氣
- Thankyou. - You're welcome.
你來拌動扳機還是我來？
You want to pull the trigger, or should I do it?
你在給我找罪受
Oh, E. You're crashin' on me, baby.
我是說你已經惹麻煩了 你還在繼續惹麻煩
Isaidyou'dcrash, andyou are crashing.
我想找些安全的地方 幫幫我
I just want to get 'em someplace safe, give 'em a chance.
他們已經是活死人了 他們沒有機會了
They're already dead, E. They got no chance.
不要跟他們一起送死
Don't go down with them.
我需要護照
I'll need passports.
還有飛機票
- [ Scoffs ] - I'll need plane tickets.
你還要把機票餵魚吃
Sure. Throw in some season tickets to the Lakers.
進去吧
Go.
你什麼都不要告訴她
[Mark] I don't wantyou to tell heranything.
我討厭撒謊 為什麼不能告訴她？
I hate lying. Why can't we tell her?
我們根本不瞭解她 但她救了我們
- We don't know anything about her. - She saved us.
因為她還不知道我們的真正身份 如果她知道了...
Because she doesn't really know who you are. If she knew-
她是我的朋友 你的朋友？
- She's my friend. - Your friend?
她是我唯一的朋友
She's the only one I have.
我不想死... 你不會死的!
- And I do not want to die with- - You're not gonna die!
不准你再說那樣的話
Don'tyou ever say that again- ever.
記住嗎？ 恩
- Okay? - Yes.
艾麗卡
[ Girl] Elektra?
怎麼了？不好看嗎？ 他們幫我改了一下容貌
What's the matter? Is something wrong? They told me to change my appearance, so-
不，你看起來不錯
No, it's- You look great.
謝謝
Thanks.
你能教我怎麼用這些東西吧 色拉鉗子
Can you show me how to use those things, the, uh, salad tongs?
鋼戟 鋼戟
- Sais. - Sais.
這個不適合你
They're not foryou.
我想學習如何防衛自己
I want to learn how to defend myself.
這是攻擊性武器 專門用來殺人
They're offensive weapons. They're for killing.
只能你用
You use them.
我不想你像我一樣
I don't want you to be like me.
但我想
I do.
你想學些真的很難的東西嗎？
Doyou wanna learn something really, really difficult?
想，是什麼？
Yeah. What?
過來
Come on.
坐下
Now sit down.
閉上眼睛 這是什麼，瑜伽術？
- Closeyour eyes. - What is this, yoga?
閉上你的眼睛然後呼吸
Just closeyour eyes and breathe.
我在呼吸 我一直在呼吸
I am breathing, I'm always breathing.
還有閉上嘴
And shut up.
安靜的坐好
Just sit quietly.
你還好嗎？
How areyou doing?
至少我們還活著 謝謝
We're still alive. Thankyou.
不要謝我，馬克
Oh, don't thank me, Mark.
你事實上根本不知道我是幹嗎的
Please, you don't really know what I was doing.
你在那裡幹什麼？
Whatyou were doing there?
我當然知道
Sure I do.
你是去那裡殺我們
You were there to kill us.
當你搬到惠爾萊特那兒的時候 我就知道你是來殺我的
I knew it as soon as you took the Wheelwright place.
我不是你適合交往的人
I'm not a good person to get involved with.
我才不管
I'm not asking for anything.
對不起
I'm sorry.
讓人討厭
Yeah, I hated that.
怎麼啦？
- [ Bird Squawks ] - What happened?
從昨天開始那隻鳥 就一直在這裡窺探
That bird's been hanging around here since late yesterday.
他們來了
They're here.
他們來了 我們開車離開
- They're here. - Let's use the truck.
來不及了 這是最快的辦法了
- We won't make it. - But that's the best way.
相信我 我們沒有時間了
Trust me. There isn't time.
從地窖走 那裡有一個密道
Use the cellar. There's a tunnel.
它橫穿果園 然後到達正北方的灌木層
Takeyou out past the orchard to the trees. Head north.
那你呢？
What aboutyou?
該死
- [Loads Gun ] - Shit.
走吧
Let's go.
當心點 保證他們的安全
- Be careful. - Keep 'em safe, E.
怪東西
- Holy- - [ Growls ]
不要告訴我你是鎮上的馬戲團的 我告訴你
Don't tell me, the circus is in town, huh? I'll tell you what.
你最好現在殺了我 我是不會告訴你任何東西的
You might as well kill me now, 'cause I ain't talking.
沒有什麼好說的
Talking is not necessary.
我答應你前面的請求
- [Yells ] - But I accept the first half ofyour proposal.
他們在樹林裡
They're in thewoods.
嗨，混蛋
Hey, dickhead.
我跟你賭一千塊 你肯定比艾麗卡早死
I'll betyou a thousand bucks you're dead before Elektra is.
等下
Hold up.
跟著我 繼續跑
Just follow me. Just keep running.
到那裡面去 馬克，快點
Get in there. Mark, come on. Go. Go.
艾麗卡
[ Quietly] Elektra.
- Elektra! - Shh.
快跑，艾比
Go! Run, Abby! Run!
快走
Go!
你為什麼不告訴我？
Why didn't you tell me?
艾麗卡 艾比不要
- Elektra! - Abby, no!
讓我幫她
Let me go!
你就是能量之源是嗎？
Ah, you are the little treasure, aren't you?
戰爭要結束了
The war is over.
戰爭才剛剛開始
The war has just begun.
退後，艾比
Move back, Abby.
她沒事的
She is safe.
後會有期，老人家
Another day, old man.
沒事了 你好好休息吧
You'll be fine. Rest now.
不要尋找你的敵人 要感應他在哪裡
Don't look foryour opponent. Know where he is.
雖然我瞎了，但我比你看到的更多 因為我不用眼睛尋找
I 'm blind, and I see more than any ofyou, because I don't look.
你沒有權利托我下水，斯蒂克
You had no right to drag me into this, Stick.
所有和幻影殺手的戰爭 都是由她而起，是嗎？
This whole warwith the Hand, everything, it's all about her, isn't it?
她是他們的能量之源
They call hertheTreasure.
她四五歲的時候就已經伸手不凡
She was aprodigy from fourorfiveyears old.
很快傳到了幻影殺手那裡
Wordgot aroundfast.
幻影想讓她助他們一臂之力 所以想偷她走
The Hand wanted her for themselves. They tried to steal her.
他爸爸又把她偷回來了 你現在又摻入這件事
- Her father spirited her away. - And you set this up-
原來都是你僱用我 和曼柯去殺他們的
The contract, McCabe, all of this- you hired me to kill them.
是你自己選擇的
You're entitled toyour opinion.
一對父女，斯蒂克你居然利用我
A father and his daughter, Stick. You manipulated me.
我有嗎？
Did I?
這原來是一個測驗
Was all this a test?
從你趕我出去那一天之後的事情 原來都是一個測驗
Everything from the day you threw me out, has it all been a test?
如果我失敗會怎麼樣？
What ifl had failed?
有些東西不是教出來的，艾麗卡
Some lessons can't be taught, Elektra.
這個需要自己參透
They must be lived to be understood.
當你來的時候，你的內心充滿憤怒
When you came here, you were filled with anger.
你的內心被 暴力和悲憤所侵蝕
All the decencyyou once had, poisoned byviolence and tragedy.
這樣是無法達到的
This is not the way.
This is not ourway.
老人家你又在上課
You talk in riddles, old man.
我想讓我的學生提高警惕性
It keeps my students alert.
我知道你的心一直是純真的
I always knew your heart was pure.
你要做的就是要超越自己
You simply needed to see it foryourself.
那艾比呢？
What about Abby?
克阮不死 她就不能離開這裡
As long as Kirigi is alive, she's only safe here.
她沒有選擇
She has no choice.
又偷偷跑到我屋來
Still breaking and entering I see.
對不起
Sorry.
你需要它的 記得要勤加練習
You'll need it. Keep practicing.
對不起我不該對你撒謊
I'm sorry I lied to you.
不用道歉 也沒有必要
Don't apologize. You did what you needed to do.
我不想對你撒謊的
I didn't wanna lie toyou.
我爸爸也不想的
Neither did my dad.
我一直很難過沒有告訴你
It made me sick not telling you.
每個人都在撒謊，艾比 沒有人不說謊的
Everybody lies, Abby. Nobody tells the truth about themselves.
包括你
Including you.
特別是我
Especially me.
解僱人，縮減工人薪水 就是那樣
- The layoffs and payroll reductions. - Like that.
恩，還有那個數數
And the, uh, the counting.
- 什麼？ - 數步數
- Sorry? - O.C.D.
我沒有數步數
I don't have O.C.D.
我小時候數過 但已經是很多年前的事情了
I had it when I was a kid, but I haven't done that in years.
你剛才還在數 當你慢慢走的時候
You were just doing it. When you walk slow like that.
那你在幹嗎？ 到底是不是在數？
What areyou doing? Areyou counting?
不要無禮
Don't mock me.
不管怎麼樣我還是你的長輩
I'm still your superior.
也許吧
Maybe.
非要跟我比試一下嗎？
Wanna find out?
我要去找我爸爸
I'm gonna go find my dad.
不要亂來
- [ Groans ] - Don't force it.
你再硬來
You're forcing it.
你很快比我更強
You'll be better than I am very soon.
我只是一個小孩 我不想留在這裡
I'm just a kid. I don't wanna stay here.
你想怎樣？
What do you want?
讓我們單獨來解決這件事情
To finish it, you and me.
我不需要斯蒂克幫忙，你不能讓你爸爸幫忙 贏者拿走一切
No help from Stick, no help from your father. Winner take all.
如果我殺了你 小孩子就是我們的
And when I kill you, the little one is ours.
你不會得逞的 她永遠是自由的
And whenyou don't, she is free forever.
同意嗎？ 同意
- Agreed? - Agreed.
那在老地方見
We will meet where it all began.
還要老地方結束我們的恩怨
And it will end where it all began.
至少我們做個了斷
Foryou, at least.
聰明的孩子
Clever girl.
艾麗卡
[ Girl] Elektra!
怎麼了？ 有什麼問題嗎？
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
我們又見面了
[Kirigi] We meet again.
現在你會記起來
Nowyou'll remember.
放開她
[Abby] Let her go!
勇敢的孩子 你調教的很好
Brave gi rl. You taught her well.
你需要一個新主人
But it's time for a new master.
這就是那個瞎子教的？
Is that what the blind man's been teachingyou?
還不夠 你要學會預見敵人
Not good enough. But you'll learn to anticipate your opponent.
艾比 我不會丟下你的
- Abby- - I'm not leaving you.
不過你確實讓人擔心 就像你一樣
- You're a pain in the ass. -Just likeyou.
紋身，能量之源就在這裡
Tattoo, the Treasure's here.
跟緊我
Stay right behind me.
跟緊點，艾比
Stay close, Abby.
艾麗卡
Elektra!
魔法耍的不錯 我以前領教過
Nice trick. I've seen it before.
艾比，你在哪裡？
Abby, where are you?
艾麗卡 可惜不是
- Elektra? - Not exactly.
我曾經是力量之源
You know, I used to be the Treasure...
我不喜歡被人代替
and I don't like being replaced.
我們兩個只能活一個
So let's keep your death between you and me.
艾比
Abby!
你不行了艾麗卡
You're slipping, Elektra.
快點，踩水，踩水...
Come on, let's go. Push, push, push.
快點，踩水、踩水...
[Father] Let's go. Let's push, push, push, push!
堅持住，艾麗卡 堅持住
- Keep going, Elektra. Keep going. - [Man ] Don't worry, Elektra.
我只是一個孩子 我會好好照顧她的
- I'm just a kid. - I'll take good care ofher.
我不想待在這裡
I don't wanna stay here.
艾麗卡
Elektra.
不要擔心，艾麗卡 我會好好照顧她的
Don't worry, Elektra. I'll take good care of her.
艾比
Abby.
該死，快點
Damn it. Come on.
我再也不害怕了
I'm not afraid anymore.
艾比
Abby.
艾比聽我說 聽我說
Abby, listen to me. Listen to me.
我知道你的心一直是純潔的
[Stick's Voice ] I always knewyourheart was pure.
但你要超越自己
You simplyneeded to see it foryourself.
嗨，女戰士
Hey, warrior girl.
快點醒來
Come here.
醒來，艾比
Come here, Abby.
我需要你 我剛剛找到你
I need you. I just found you.
我剛剛找到你
I just found you.
嗨
Hi.
謝謝
Thankyou.
對不起
Sorry.
你真討厭
Yeah, I hated that.
下一步準備幹什麼，克阮已經死了 沒有人追殺你了
So, what's next? Kirigi's gone. No one's afteryou.
去上學？
Back to school?
到海灘來個日光浴 還有冰激凌
- Go to the beach and get a tan. - And get ice cream.
噢
[ Laughs ] Oh.
是你重新給我生命
You gave me my life back.
是你讓我參悟我的人生
You gave me mine.
我還能再見到你嗎？
Will I seeyou again?
我們會在意念內相會
We'll find each other.
希望她不要走我的路
Please don't let her be like me.
為什麼不？
Whynot?
其實你還不錯
You didn't turn out so bad.
我不想看她太生活的太累
I don't want it to be so hard for her.
這個要由她來決定
That's up to her.
你復活的第二次生命 是不是跟原來的大所不同？
Anyway, your second life's never really likeyour first, is it?
有時候...
Sometimes...
比以前的生活更精彩
it's even better.